const chapter1 = [
    {
        id: 1,
        question: "What was Salmaâ€™s Physical appearance?",
        answer: "Salma was a fair complexioned girl, tall, slim and rather busty.",
        chapter: "1"
    },
    {
        id: 2,
        question: "What does Selma believe about Lecturers?",
        answer: "University Lecturers take money from boys and ask girls on a date",
        chapter: "1",
    },
    {
        id: 3,
        question: "Why was the HOD close to Ummi?",
        answer: "She knows her husband very well and was even the one who worked her admission.",
        chapter: "1",
    },
    {
        id: 4,
        question: "Why was the People of Lafayette happy?",
        answer: "Because their daughter Ummi was going to the University.",
        chapter: "1",
    },
    {
        id: 5,
        question: "What was the first thing that struck Ummi in school?",
        answer: "The carefree attitude of University students.",
        chapter: "1",
    },
    {
        id: 6,
        question: "According to Ummi, when should you call someone dear",
        answer: "Only when they mean something to you.",
        chapter: "1",
    },
    {
        id: 7,
        question: "After registration, when did Salma and Ummi meet again?",
        answer: "A few months later",
        chapter: "1",
    },
    {
        id: 8,
        question: "Describe the Secretary to the HOD",
        answer: "She was busy hitting at the computer, a very focused person and a woman of few words.",
        chapter: "1",
    },
    {
        id: 9,
        question: "hat did Ummi and her husband conclude?",
        answer: "The recalcitrant male will also misbehave irrespective of what the woman wears.",
        chapter: "1",
    },
    {
        id: 10,
        question: "What tribe and religion was the HOD, Dr Samuel Johnson.",
        answer: "Christian and Yoruba Man.",
        chapter: "1",
    },
]

export {chapter1}